{
    "id": "6c4d7a811b4748f3a5980f66cca085ed",
    "title": "Participles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. a loud sound, we rushed out of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy cried, ……………….. that he would be whipped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thinking",
                "thought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. by the rain, we took shelter under a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Driven",
                "Driving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw a goods train ………………… with wheat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loading",
                "loaded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. wealth is a curse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Ill-getting",
                "Ill-gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… with grief she threw herself on the body.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Stricken",
                "Striking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… with age the old man tottered along.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bent",
                "Bending"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A ……………… stone gathers no moss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rolling",
                "rolled"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are fighting a ………………. battle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "losing",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t cry over ……………….. milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spilling",
                "spilt"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}